A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1 FA427
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative, 1952, 1954-2006; 1; 108.25 Cubic Feet 246 document boxes.
  - ACC records of the JDR 3rd Fund, 1952, 1954-1955, 1957-1989; 1
    - Director's Office, 1955, 1957-1989; 3
      - U. S. Organizations, 1959-1987; 22
        - American Dance Guild, 1976-1977 (Box 94, Folder 3269)
        - American Field Service, 1964-1966, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 3270)
        - American Friends of Attingham, Inc.-Ariel Chamber Ensemble, Inc., 1963-1965, 1967, 1969-1970, 1972-1974, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 3271)
        - American International Music Fund, 1958-1959, 1962-1963, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 3272)
        - American National Theatre and Academy, 1962, 1964, 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 3273)
        - American Society for Eastern Arts, Correspondence, 1963-1973, 1975-1976, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 3274)
        - American Society for Eastern Arts, Printed Material, 1965-1969, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 3275)
        - American Universities Field Staff, 1964-1969, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 3276)
        - Artist's Market-Audubon Quartet, 1969-1970, 1973-1980 (Box 95, Folder 3277)
        - Asian Media Committee, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3278)
        - Asian Theatre Artists, 1962-1965, 1970, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 3279)
        - Associated Councils of the Arts, 1965-1971, 1975-1976 (Box 95, Folder 3280)
        - Association of American Colleges, 1961-1969 (Box 95, Folder 3281)
        - B, 1964, 1970-1972, 1974-1979, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 3282)
        - Baltimore International Theatre Festival, (Formerly, the New Theatre Festival), 1973, 1976-1979 (Box 96, Folder 3283)
        - Basement Workshops Inc., Yellow Pearl Project, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 3284)
        - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1965-1966, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 3285)
        - Business Committee for the Arts, 1968-1971, 1974, 1976, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 3286)
        - Cable Arts Foundation-Chautaqua, 1964, 1968-1970, 1972-1979, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 3287)
        - Cantometrics Project, 1967-1971 (Box 96, Folder 3288)
        - Centre for Cross Cultural Communication, 1963-1965 (Box 96, Folder 3289)
        - Chestnut Hill Concerts-Cultural Survival, Inc., 1962, 1964-1968, 1970-1980, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 3290)
        - China Study Group on Environmental Issues, 1976-1980 (Box 97, Folder 3291)
        - City Center of Music and Drama, 1971-1972 (Box 97, Folder 3292)
        - College Art Association of America, 1968, 1973, 1976-1979 (Box 97, Folder 3293)
        - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1963, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 3294)
        - Columbia Artists Management, Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 97, Folder 3295)
        - Committee to Aid Indochinese Refugees, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 3296)
        - Composer's Showcase, 1961, 1963, 1965-1967, 1969-1972 (Box 97, Folder 3297)
        - Conference on Chinese Oral & Performing Literature, Chinoperl News, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 3298)
        - Coordinating Council for International Issues, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 3299)
        - D, 1967-1968, 1970-1971, 1973, 1975, 1977-1978 (Box 97, Folder 3300)
        - Facets Multimedia, Inc.-Festival Orchestra Society, 1961-1966, 1968, 1972, 1976-1977 (Box 97, Folder 3301)
        - First Chamber Dance Company-The Fund for Education in World Order, 1964-1965, 1968, 1973-1975, 1979-1980 (Box 97, Folder 3302)
        - Foreign Policy Association, 1964, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 3303)
        - Franklin Book Programs, 1962-1966, 1969-1970 (Box 98, Folder 3304)
        - G, 1975, 1979 (Box 98, Folder 3305)
        - Global Village Video Study Center, 1973-1975, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 3306)
        - H, 1962-1963, 1968-1969, 1972, 1975-1976, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 3307)
        - Hawkins (Erick) Dance Company, 1959-1960, 1964-1966, 1968, 1972-1974 (Box 98, Folder 3308)
        - IBM-The Institute of Japanese-American Cultural Research, Inc., 1963-1965, 1970-1971, 1973, 1976-1978, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 3309)
        - Indo-American Performing Arts Center, 1967, 1972-1973 (Box 98, Folder 3310)
        - Institute for Advanced Studies in Theatre Arts, 1961-1969, 1974, 1979 (Box 98, Folder 3311)
        - Institute for International Studies & Training-International Visitors Center, Inc., 1964-1965, 1968, 1970-1971, 1973-1974, 1976, 1978-1980 (Box 99, Folder 3312)
        - Institute for the Study of Universal History of Arts and Artifacts, 1973-1977 (Box 99, Folder 3313)
        - Institute of Contemporary Arts, 1964, 1967-1968, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 3314)
        - Institute for Current World Affairs, 1964, 1966-1971 (Box 99, Folder 3315)
        - International Hospitality Center, 1973, 1976-1977 (Box 99, Folder 3316)
        - J, 1965-1966, 1971, 1974-1976 (Box 99, Folder 3317)
        - K, 1964, 1966, 1968-1969, 1973, 1975-1977, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 3318)
        - Kalmuk Community, 1964, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 3319)
        - L, 1966, 1970-1972, 1976, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 3320)
        - M, 1965-1966, 1971-1978 (Box 100, Folder 3321)
        - The MacDowell Colony, 1964-1965, 1968-1970 (Box 100, Folder 3322)
        - Midtown International Center, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 3323)
        - N, 1964-1965, 1968-1969, 1971, 1975, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 3324)
        - National Architectural Accrediting Board, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 100, Folder 3325)
        - National Art Education Association, 1971, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 3326)
        - National Educational Television, 1966-1967, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 3327)
        - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1964-1965, 1968-1970, 1972-1973 (Box 100, Folder 3328)
        - O, 1965, 1974, 1976, 1978-1979 (Box 101, Folder 3329)
        - P, 1968, 1970-1974, 1976-1978, 1980, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 3330)
        - Pan Pacific & Southwest Asia Women's Association, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 3331)
        - R, 1965, 1967, 1974-1975, 1979, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 3332)
        - S, 1964-1967, 1970-1973, 1975, 1977-1981 (Box 101, Folder 3333)
        - Society for Asian Art, 1964, 1967-1968, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 3334)
        - T, 1972-1976, 1978-1980, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 3335)
        - Theater in the Street, 1966-1967, 1969, 1971-1973 (Box 101, Folder 3336)
        - U-V, 1968-1969, 1971, 1973, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 3337)
        - W, 1965-1966, 1968-1972, 1974, 1977, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 3338)
        - Y-Z, 1970, 1975-1976 (Box 102, Folder 3339)
        - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA), 1968-1969 (Box 102, Folder 3340)
    - Comptroller's Office, 1984-1988; 4
      - Audit, Docket Backup Materials, 1984 December (Box 102, Folder 3341)
      - Audit, Grants Payment Summaries, 1985 (Box 102, Folder 3342)
      - Audit, Indo-U.S. Subcommission on Education and Culture, 1985 March (Box 102, Folder 3343)
      - Audit, #202R, Grants Payable, Restricted, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 3345)
      - Audit, #202, Grants Payable, Unrestricted, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 3344)
      - Audit, ACC, Board of Trustees Meeting, Agenda, 1987 November 20 (Box 102, Folder 3346)
      - Audit, Grants, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 3347)
      - Audit, #202, Grants Payable, Unrestricted, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 3348)
      - Audit, #202R, Grants Payable, Restricted, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 3349)
      - Audit, #202 Grants Payable, Unrestricted, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 3350)
      - Audit, #202R, Grants Payable, Restricted, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 3351)
      - Audit, Schedule of Grants Appropriated and Payable, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 3352)
      - Hong Kong, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 3353)
    - Trip Notes, 1966-1989; 5
      Subseries 1: Lanier, Richard S. Subseries 2: Lanier, Richard S. and Others Subseries 3: Others
      - Lanier, Richard S., 1971-1989; 1
        - American Theater Association, New Orleans, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 3354)
        - Asia Trip, 1973 February-March (Box 102, Folder 3355)
        - Asia Trip, 1976 February 17-March 20 (Box 102, Folder 3356)
        - Asia Trip, Book Purchases, 1976 February-March (Box 102, Folder 3357)
        - Asia Trip, 1976 November-December (Box 102, Folder 3358)
        - Asia Trip, 1977 February-March (Box 102, Folder 3359)
        - Asia Trip, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 3360)
        - Asia Trip, 1980 April-May (Box 102, Folder 3361)
        - Asia Trip: China, Japan, Korea, Hong Kong, 1982-1983 (Box 102, Folder 3362)
        - Asia & Europe Trip, Book Purchases, 1975 February 22-April 10 (Box 102, Folder 3363)
        - Association of Asian Studies, Los Angeles, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 3364)
        - Bangkok, 1978, 1980-1981, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 3365)
        - Bangladesh & Pakistan, 1976-1977, 1980, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 3366)
        - Berlin, 1977 May (Box 102, Folder 3367)
        - Ceylon/Sri Lanka, 1975 Winter (Box 103, Folder 3368)
        - China, 1982 October (Box 103, Folder 3369)
        - College Art Association of America, New Orleans, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 3370)
        - College Art Association of America, Washington D. C., 1979 (Box 103, Folder 3371)
        - Copenhagen, 1977 May (Box 103, Folder 3372)
        - Dacca, 1977 March, 1980 April (Box 103, Folder 3373)
        - England, 1973 January-March, 1972-1973 (Box 103, Folder 3374)
        - England, 1975 Winter (Box 103, Folder 3375)
        - Europe-Asia, 1975 February 22-April 10 (Box 103, Folder 3376)
        - France, 1973 January-March (Box 103, Folder 3377)
        - Germany, 1975 Winter (Box 103, Folder 3378)
        - Greece, 1975 Winter (Box 103, Folder 3379)
        - Hong Kong, 1973 January-March (Box 103, Folder 3380)
        - Hong Kong, 1975 Winter (Box 103, Folder 3381)
        - Hong Kong, 1976 March (Box 103, Folder 3382)
        - Hong Kong, 1986, 1982-1983, 1985-1986 (Box 103, Folder 3383)
        - Hong Kong, Business Cards Received, 1985 May, 1984-1986 (Box 103, Folder 3384)
        - Hong Kong, Business Cards Received, 1986 November (Box 103, Folder 3385)
        - Hong Kong, Business Cards Received from Previous Hong Kong Trip, 1986 November (Box 103, Folder 3386)
        - Hong Kong, Jakarata, Tokyo, 1985 November, 1986 March (Box 103, Folder 3387)
        - Hong Kong & Tokyo, 1987 March (Box 103, Folder 3388)
        - Hong Kong & Tokyo, 1988 November 8-17 (Box 103, Folder 3389)
        - Honolulu, 1975 Winter, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 3390)
        - Honolulu, 1976 December (Box 103, Folder 3391)
        - India Trip, 1975, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 3392)
        - India, 1976 February-March (Box 103, Folder 3393)
        - India,1980 April, 1978, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 3394)
        - India Trip, 1988 December 18-1989 January 2 (Box 103, Folder 3395)
        - India, Applicants, Partial Listing, 1977 March (Box 103, Folder 3396)
        - India, New Delhi & Dharmsala, 1978 February, 1976, 1978, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 3397)
        - India, South, 1980-1982 (Box 103, Folder 3398)
        - Indonesia, 1973 January-March (Box 104, Folder 3399)
        - Indonesia, 1976 March (Box 104, Folder 3400)
        - Indonesia, 1981 June (Box 104, Folder 3401)
        - Iran, 1973 January-March (Box 104, Folder 3402)
        - Italy, 1973 January-March, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 3403)
        - Japan, 1973 January-March, 1971-1973 (Box 104, Folder 3404)
        - Japan, 1975 Winter, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 3405)
        - Japan, 1976 November-December, 1974, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 3406)
        - Japan, All Other Cities, 1981 June, 1974, 1976, 1978, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 3407)
        - Japan, Old Tokyo, 1974, 1976-1978, 1980-1983 (Box 104, Folder 3408)
        - Korea, 1976 December, 1975-1976 (Box 104, Folder 3409)
        - Leningrad, 1977 May (Box 104, Folder 3410)
        - London, 1976 February (Box 104, Folder 3411)
        - London, 1984 March, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 104, Folder 3412)
        - Los Angeles, 1973 January-March (Box 104, Folder 3413)
        - Los Angeles, 1977 March, 1976-1977 (Box 104, Folder 3414)
        - Malaysia, 1975, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 3415)
        - Malaysia, 1975 Winter (Box 104, Folder 3416)
        - Malaysia, 1977 March, 1975, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 3417)
        - Manila, 1977 March, 1975, 1977, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 3418)
        - Manila, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 3419)
        - Manila, 1981 June (Box 104, Folder 3420)
        - Moscow, 1977 May (Box 104, Folder 3421)
        - National Endowment for the Arts, Washington, D. C., 1980 (Box 104, Folder 3422)
        - Nepal, 1976 March (Box 104, Folder 2423)
        - Netherlands, 1975 Winter (Box 104, Folder 3424)
        - New Delhi, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 3425)
        - Osaka, 1982 October, 1974, 1976, 1978, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 3426)
        - Pakistan, 1973 January-March, 1972-1973 (Box 104, Folder 3427)
        - Pakistan, 1976 February (Box 104, Folder 3428)
        - Paris, 1978 February, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 3429)
        - Paris, 1983 July, 1977-1978, 1980, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 3430)
        - Philippines, 1975 Winter (Box 104, Folder 3431)
        - Rome, 1978 February, 1973, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 3432)
        - San Francisco, 1975 Winter (Box 104, Folder 3433)
        - San Francisco, 1976 December (Box 105, Folder 3434)
        - San Francisco and Kansas City, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 3435)
        - Seattle, 1976 December (Box 105, Folder 3436)
        - Seoul, 1984 March, 1975-1976, 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 3437)
        - Singapore, 1975 Winter (Box 105, Folder 3438)
        - Stockholm, 1977 May (Box 105, Folder 3439)
        - Taiwan, 1973 January-March (Box 105, Folder 3440)
        - Taiwan, 1976 March (Box 105, Folder 3441)
        - Taiwan, 1978 February (Box 105, Folder 3442)
        - Tehran, 1977 February (Box 105, Folder 3443)
        - Thailand, 1973 January-March (Box 105, Folder 3444)
        - Thailand, 1975 Winter, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 3445)
        - Thailand, 1976 March (Box 105, Folder 3446)
        - Thailand & Bangladesh, 1976-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 105, Folder 3447)
        - Tokyo, Business Cards Received, 1986 November (Box 105, Folder 3448)
        - Tokyo, Business Cards Received from Previous Trip, 1986 November (Box 105, Folder 3449)
        - Tokyo & Hong Kong, 1989 November 6-17 (Box 105, Folder 3450)
        - Tokyo & Kyoto, 1983, 1974, 1976, 1978, 1982-1983 (Box 105, Folder 3451)
        - Tokyo Trip, 2nd Half, Restaurants & Galleries, 1985 November (Box 105, Folder 3452)
        - Tokyo Trip & Meeting Notes, 1983 April 15-22 (Box 105, Folder 3453)
        - Turkey, 1973 January-March (Box 105, Folder 3454)
        - Vienna, 1976 February (Box 105, Folder 3455)
        - Washington, D. C., 1979 (Box 105, Folder 3456)
        - Washington, D. C., 1985 June 12-14 (Box 105, Folder 3457)
      - Lanier, Richard S. and Others, 1971-1974, 1976-1978, 1980-1982; 2
        - Lanier, Richard S. & Maureen Liebl, North India, 1974, 1976, 1978, 1980-1982 (Box 105, Folder 3458)
        - Lanier, Richard S. & Maureen Liebl, Pakistan, 1980 April & 1982, 1976-1977, 1980-1982 (Box 105, Folder 3459)
        - McCray, Porter A. & Richard S. Lanier, Asia Trip, 1972-1973 January-March (Box 105, Folder 3460)
        - McCray, Porter A. & Richard S. Lanier, Bangladesh, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 3461)
        - McCray, Porter A. & Richard S. Lanier, Cambodia (Box 106, Folder 3462)
        - McCray, Porter A. & Richard S. Lanier, Indonesia, 1971-1972 (Box 106, Folder 3463)
        - McCray, Porter A. & Richard S. Lanier, Korea, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 3464)
        - McCray, Porter A. & Richard S. Lanier, Malaysia, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 3465)
        - McCray, Porter A. & Richard S. Lanier, Nepal, 1972-1973 (Box 106, Folder 3466)
        - McCray, Porter A. & Richard S. Lanier, Pakistan, 1972-1973 (Box 106, Folder 3467)
        - McCray, Porter A. & Richard S. Lanier, Philippines, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 3468)
      - Others, 1966-1972, 1975-1978, 1980; 3
        - Asia Trip, By Board or Others, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 3469)
        - Campbell, Alan, Asia Trip, 1967-1968 (Box 106, Folder 3470)
        - Campbell, Alan, Asia Trip, 1969-1970 (Box 106, Folder 3471)
        - Campbell, Alan, Asia Trip, 1971-1972 (Box 106, Folder 3472)
        - Glaeser, Elizabeth B., Asia Trip, 1966-1967 (Box 106, Folder 3473)
        - Glaeser, Elizabeth B., Asia Trip, 1971-1972 (Box 106, Folder 3474)
        - Hong Kong (Box 106, Folder 3475)
        - India, Applicants, Partial Listing, 1978 February (Box 106, Folder 3476)
        - Kanach, Jeanne, Asian Trip, Personal, 1980 (Box 106, Folder 3477)
        - Liebl, Maureen, Asia Trips, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 3478)
        - Miscellaneous Addresses (Box 106, Folder 3479)
        - Smith, Datus C., Jr., Asia Trip, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 3480)
        - Wheeler, Miki K., Asia Trip, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 3481)
    - International Council of Museums (ICOM) News Bulletin, 1970-1979; 6
      - ICOM News, Vol. 23, Number 1-4, 1970 (Box 106, Folder 3482)
      - ICOM News, Vol. 24, Number 1-4, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 3483)
      - ICOM News, Vol. 25, Number 1-2 & 4, 1972 (Box 107, Folder 3484)
      - ICOM News, Vol. 26, Number 1-4, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 3485)
      - ICOM News, Vol. 27, Numbers 1-4, 1974 (Box 107, Folder 3485B)
      - ICOM News, Vol. 28, Number 1-3, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 3486)
      - ICOM News, Vol. 29, Numbers 1-4, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 3487)
      - ICOM News, Vol. 30, Number 1-3, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 3488)
      - ICOM News, Vol. 31, Numbers 1-4, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 3489)
      - ICOM News, Vol. 32, Numbers 1-4, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 3490)
  - ACC records, 1955-1958, 1960-2006; 2
    Materials pertain to the administrative offices of the Asian Cultural Council with some early records of the Asian Cultural Program of the JDR 3rd Fund.
    Series 1: Board of Trustees Series 2: Richard S. Lanier records Series 3: Foreign Office Series 4: Program Files Series 5: Director's Office Series 6: Japan-U. S. Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Series 7: Out of Program Series 8: Annual Reports
    - Board of Trustees, 1990-2000; 1
      - Executive Committee, 1990 February 21 (Box 108, Folder 3491)
      - Docket Material, 1990 May 31 (Box 108, Folder 3492)
      - Docket Material, 1990 November 29 (Box 108, Folder 3493)
      - Executive Committee, 1991 February 11 (Box 108, Folder 3494)
      - Docket Material, 1991 June 21 (Box 108, Folder 3495)
      - Docket Material, 1991 December 13 (Box 108, Folder 3496)
      - Executive Committee, 1992 February 26 (Box 108, Folder 3496)
      - Docket Material, 1992 June 16 (Box 108, Folder 3497)
      - Docket Material, 1992 December 16 (Box 108, Folder 3498)
      - Executive Committee, 1993 February 18 (Box 108, Folder 3499)
      - Docket Material, 1993 May 18 (Box 108, Folder 3500)
      - Docket Material, 1993 December 15 (Box 108, Folder 3501)
      - Executive Committee, 1994 March 4, April 15 (Box 109, Folder 3502)
      - Docket Material, 1994 May 18 (Box 109, Folder 3503)
      - Docket Material, 1994 November 22 (Box 109, Folder 3504)
      - Executive Committee, 1995 February 6 (Box 109, Folder 3505)
      - Docket Material, 1995 June 5 (Box 109, Folder 3506)
      - Executive Committee, 1995 September 19 (Box 109, Folder 3507)
      - Docket Material, Tokyo, Japan, 1995 October 28 (Box 109, Folder 3508)
      - Executive Committee, 1996 February 20 (Box 109, Folder 3509)
      - Docket Material, 1996 June 5 (Box 109, Folder 3510)
      - Docket Material, 1996 December 2 (Box 109, Folder 3511)
      - Executive Committee, 1997 February 19 (Box 109, Folder 3512)
      - Docket Material, 1997 June 2 (Box 109, Folder 3513)
      - Docket Material, 1997 December 2 (Box 109, Folder 3514)
      - Executive Meeting, 1998 February 13 (Box 110, Folder 3515)
      - Docket Material, 1998 June 9 (Box 110, Folder 3516)
      - Docket Material, 1998 October 25 (Box 110, Folder 3517)
      - Executive Committee, 1999 February 18 (Box 110, Folder 3518)
      - Docket Material, 1999 May 25 (Box 110, Folder 3519)
      - Docket Material, 1999 November 30 (Box 110, Folder 3520)
      - Executive Committee, 2000 February 15 (Box 110, Folder 3521)
      - Docket Material, 2000 June 5 (Box 110, Folder 3522)
      - Docket Material, 2000 December 4 (Box 110, Folder 3523)
    - Richard S. Lanier records, 1978-1987, 1989-2001; 2
      - ACC, Fellowship/Conservation, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 3524)
      - ACC, Friends in Hong Kong, 1990, 1992-1994, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 3525)
      - ACC, Hong Kong, 1992, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 3526)
      - ACC, Hong Kong, 1992, 1994, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 3527)
      - ACC, Hong Kong, 1992-1994, 1997-1999 (Box 111, Folder 3528)
      - ACC, Hong Kong, Trip, 1996 November (Box 111, Folder 3529)
      - ACC, International Advisory Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 111, Folder 3530)
      - ACC, Japan, Kochi, Georg, 1992-1993, 1996, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 3531)
      - ACC, List of Grants, 1980-1982 (Box 111, Folder 3532)
      - ACC, Manila, 1998 October (Box 111, Folder 3533)
      - ACC, Miscellaneous, 1991-1996, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 3534)
      - ACC, Taiwan, 1994-1995, 1997 (Box 111, Folder 3535)
      - ACC, Trustees, 1992, 1997 (Box 111, Folder 3536)
      - ACC/Luce Foundation, Art History Seminars in China (Box 111, Folder 3537)
      - Allana, Amal, India, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 3538)
      - Alvarez, Heherson T., 1993 (Box 111, Folder 3539)
      - American-Bhutan Council, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 3540)
      - American Express Foundation, Fundraising, 1981-1982, 1984, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 3541)
      - AMAX Foundation, Fundraising, 1980-1981 (Box 111, Folder 3542)
      - Ashton, Dore, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 3543)
      - The Asia Foundation, 1992, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 3544)
      - Asia Society, Administration, 1980-1982 (Box 111, Folder 3545)
      - Asia Society, Bill McKeever, 1993-1994 (Box 111, Folder 3546)
      - Asian Trip, 1995 October, 1995-1996 (Box 111, Folder 3547)
      - Avitabile, Gunhild, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 3548)
      - Awasthi, Suresh, India, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 3549)
      - Bansal, Rajendra, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 3550)
      - Baron, Barnett F., Save the Children, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 3551)
      - Barnett, John, University of New Hampshire, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 3552)
      - Bay Foundation, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 3553)
      - Bechtel Corporation, Fundraising, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 3554)
      - Behl, Benoy K., Benoy K. Behl Films, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 3555)
      - Bettag, Claire, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 3556)
      - Bickford, George, Fundraising, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 3557)
      - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller Memorial Fund Committee in Tokyo, 1993-1995 (Box 112, Folder 3558)
      - Bourgeois, Louise, Asian Files, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 3559)
      - Brandon, James, University of Hawaii, 1994-1995 (Box 112, Folder 3560)
      - Brouwer, Robert & Mon Brouwer, 1991-1992 (Box 112, Folder 3561)
      - Buckley, J. Russell, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 3562)
      - Buddhist Perception of Nature, Fundraising, 1985-1987 (Box 112, Folder 3563)
      - Center for U.S.-China Arts Exchange, Possible Institutional Relationship, Administrative, 1984-1985 (Box 112, Folder 3564)
      - Champion International, Proposal, 1985 (Box 112, Folder 3565)
      - Chase Manhattan Bank, Fundraising, 1981-1985 (Box 112, Folder 3566)
      - Ching, Chiang, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 3567)
      - Citibank, Fundraising, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 3568)
      - Consulate General of Japan, 1998-1999 (Box 112, Folder 3569)
      - Coopers & Lybrand, 1991-1993 (Box 112, Folder 3570)
      - Curran, Catherine, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 3571)
      - Currimbhoy, Suraiya, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 3572)
      - Dehejia, Vidya, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 3573)
      - Development, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 3574)
      - Dhamija, Jasleen, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 3575)
      - Dharma Kusuma Award, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 3576)
      - Diskul, Mom Chao Subhardadis, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 3577)
      - Dong Soong Art Center, Korea, 1996-1997 (Box 112, Folder 3578)